<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<data>
	<section>
		<name>Why Sliday?</name>
		<body>
			<![CDATA[
				<img src="http://sliday.com/images/about/sliday_collage_cut2.jpg" width="590" height="160"/> <br>
				Think about Sliday as of the bridge between yourself and the world. You have a talent and works to show - we know the best possible way of doing it. Talk to us today - become famous tomorrow. We specialise in effective presentation of visual materials in Internet by using all the advantages of the most progressive and flexible flash-technology of today. We seek to help talented artists, photographs and companies to impress their clients by representing in Internet their achievements in the most favourable light. The experience that we have gained through working with photographs, designers and architects, allows us to create for you websites which display most precisely and strikingly all your talents, products and achievements. We work all over the world. Our headquarters is located in New Zealand, and we have European office in Moscow.
			]]>
		</body>
	</section>
	<section>
		<name>Who are Sliday?</name>
		<body>
			Gurus in creating online flash portfolios for anyone who needs a stunning presentation on the web Sliday is a quick, efficient company with prompt follow up and endless support with your project. That brings us a mile ahead of any competitor around. We have a competitive pricing which will suit any pocket and any budget. Put an excellent customer service and right attitude on top, don't worry that's absolutely free of charge. Don't hesitate and email us today, make your dream come true very shortly after. Your friendly Sliday team.
		</body>
	</section>
	<section>
		<name>Testimonials</name>
		<body>
			They created a brilliant site! Many thanks!! All my clients will be crazy about it! Mega Professionals. Will recommend them to my friends and partners. I am extremely delighted! - Maximo Gaia, San Francisco, CA , USA Thanks a lot for your hard work guys! Web site was developed as agreed, in a good timely manner and everything is perfect! Well done! - Andre Haruk, Auckland, New Zealand
		</body>
	</section>
</data>